JEAN-BAPTISTE **Bohiki**

FRONT-END
WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT DETAILS

Address: Benin (ready to relocate or work according to any timezone)

Email: jbbohiki@gmail.com
Portfolio: https://flemking.com
LinkedIn: @flemking
GitHub: @flemking

PERSONAL SUMMARY

As a Web Developer and Digital Marketing Expert, I would like to put at your disposal my knowledge in these different fields. I have been working as a freelancer in these fields for 4 years and I am convinced that the skills and experiences I have acquired during these last 4 years could make me an ideal candidate.

KEY COMPETENCIES

- · HTML/CSS/JAVASCRIPT/PYTHON
- React.js/Next.js
- Tailwindcss/SASS
- · PHP/MySQL/Django
- · Figma/Adobe XD/Adobe Photoshop
- UX/UI Design
- WordPress/WebFlow/Shopify
- Creation and optimization of advertising campaigns.
- etc...

Languages: French / English
My Certifications: <u>Check on GitHub</u>

WORK EXPERIENCES

Frontend Web Developer

Freelance | 2018 - present

Once I graduated from high school in 2017, I started learning web development by myself and began freelancing.

Community Manager / Marketing Specialist

ARLICA & AUCERPI CONSULTANT | 2020 - 2021

In 2020 I started working part-time for two local companies (with the same CEO). I'm in charge of all the media content and all the social networks related to the companies.

Digital Marketing Expert

Freelance | 2019 - present

I also learned about digital marketing because I used to do a lot of e-commerce sites... so I have a great understanding and experience in managing Google and Facebook ads.

FORMATIONS

Scrimba

Frontend Developer Carrier Path Certificate | 2021

The program contains 14 modules. All modules are filled with interactive coding challenges to ensure that I don't fall off the wagon. I have learned HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, UI design, career strategy, and more.

Harvard University

Computer Science 50 | 2020 - 2021

A course taught by David J. Malan, CS50x teaches me how to think algorithmically and solve problems efficiently. Topics include abstraction, algorithms, data structures, encapsulation, resource management, security, software engineering, and web development. Languages include C, Python, SQL, and JavaScript plus CSS and HTML. Problem sets inspired by real-world domains of biology, cryptography, finance, forensics, and gaming.

BAC+2 in Economic Statistics (unfinished curriculum)

Economic Statistics | 2017 - 2019

Due to several circumstances, I was not able to finish my degree but I kept my sense of statistical analysis which I use when analyzing data from advertising campaigns.

WHY ME?

I see myself as a person with a versatile skill-set, a fast learner, integrity, results-driven, smart worker and I have the willingness to always satisfy the customers.

Now, I want to take my career to another level. I want to quit freelancing works and start working with a great team, full-time.